We have these three midlines within us.
We have already integrated the first midline, which is the midline, let's say,
the notochordal line.
This notochordal midline establishes the posterior midline
which in turn establishes the anterior midline.
We have this urogenital area within us.
The area where we can sit on the earth,
urogenital, the matrix, the matter,
the reality.
I will be well seated on my heels.
These were the others who said
that we should learn to breathe all the way into our heels.
We will have good breathing in our heels.
This is the mineral kingdom.
When you are grounded in your mineral kingdom,
when you are well in your reality,
when you are well in your urogenital reproductive system,
you are well in your plant kingdom.
This means that you are well in your metabolic kingdom.
The plant kingdom is also related to your
emotions.
Emotions are liquid.
This is the liquids.
And when you are well there, you can be well in your rhythmic kingdom.
When you are well in your rhythms, you are well anchored in your rhythms,
you are well in your animal kingdom.
Everything rhythmic is here.
And when you are well,
in there, you can connect to your kingdom
thank you, Marie. It's a pleasure.
And there, you can learn to breathe well here.
What is it?
I am well in my
neurosensory kingdom, I am no longer judging.
I discern.
My vision opens up.
I am well in my discernment,
I am well in my rhythms.
When I am well in my rhythms, I am well in my emotions.
When I am well in my emotions, I come back well to my earth.
I settle well on the earth.